<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>nipkow's stuff</title><subtitle>A home for various random things made by/related to nipkow.</subtitle> <updated>2024-01-28T10:18:10-03:00</updated> <author> <name>nipkow</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2024 nipkow </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>BloodRayne_tweaks - Fixes and tweaks for BloodRayne Terminal Cut</title><link href="/BloodRayne_tweaks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BloodRayne_tweaks - Fixes and tweaks for BloodRayne Terminal Cut" /><published>2021-07-22T22:20:00-03:00</published> <updated>2021-08-08T13:24:32-03:00</updated> <id>/BloodRayne_tweaks/</id> <content src="/BloodRayne_tweaks/" /> <author> <name>nipkow</name> </author> <summary> A project designed to fix and tweak BloodRayne: Terminal Cut on Steam. Current features Fix HUD - Fix the HUD, moving it further away from the center of the screen. Comparison: Before After Ultrawide Lock cursor to game window - Both the original version and the “Terminal Cut” have problems with multi-monitor s... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>re4_tweaks - Fixes and tweaks for the Steam version of Resident Evil 4</title><link href="/re4_tweaks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="re4_tweaks - Fixes and tweaks for the Steam version of Resident Evil 4" /><published>2021-02-28T22:20:00-03:00</published> <updated>2022-01-27T16:06:58-03:00</updated> <id>/re4_tweaks/</id> <content src="/re4_tweaks/" /> <author> <name>nipkow</name> </author> <summary> A project designed to fix and tweak the “UHD” port of Resident Evil 4 on Steam. Current features Increase FOV - Increases the default FOV. Useful to prevent motion sickness in some people. Fix ultrawide aspect ratio - Fixes the incorrect aspect ratio when playing in ultrawide resolutions, preventing the image from being cut off and the HUD appearing off-screen. Only tested... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Chaotic;Head - Fixing Chaos;Head</title><link href="/ChaoticHead/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaotic;Head - Fixing Chaos;Head" /><published>2019-03-20T22:20:00-03:00</published> <updated>2024-01-28T10:17:17-03:00</updated> <id>/ChaoticHead/</id> <content src="/ChaoticHead/" /> <author> <name>nipkow</name> </author> <summary> Chaotic;Head is a Chaos;Head patch created to improve its stability and playability. Chaos;Head is a visual novel developed by 5pb. and Nitroplus, but unlike its more popular “cousin” Steins;Gate, Chaos;Head was never localized. Fans took it upon themselves to translate the whole game unofficially, but they couldn’t predict just how terrible the game’s engine was. “N2System” as it is called, i... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Steins;Gate Steam - HQ FMV Project</title><link href="/SteinsGate-FMV-Project/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Steins;Gate Steam - HQ FMV Project" /><published>2018-11-04T23:20:00-02:00</published> <updated>2022-11-11T17:31:48-03:00</updated> <id>/SteinsGate-FMV-Project/</id> <content src="/SteinsGate-FMV-Project/" /> <author> <name>nipkow</name> </author> <summary> When the Steam version of Steins;Gate was produced, the developers decided to use a very well known and often reliable video codec - Bink. Bink can be an amazing compressor, but whoever is encoding videos has to be very careful, otherwise Bink will destroy the video in order to achieve a small file size. Suffice to say, Steins;Gate’s bink videos are really, really, horribly compressed. As so... </summary> </entry> </feed>
